(
"ai_sub_version": "2.8.2",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"ollama_search": (
"key": "**********"
),
"web_search_tool": "ollama",
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": "libx264"
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
3D新衣装お披露目！
重大告知
[3D New Outfit Reveal!]
[Major Announcements]
RACING TOWARDS HOPE
IRyS
Daisuke
Lyrics: Y&Co. Music: 田村哲也
[Song: Daisuke]
[Lyrics: Y&Co. Music: Tetsuya Tamura]
Daisuke!
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy.
I'm a natural girl,
but you're prince for me.
Everyday wondering how I become your girl.
Everynight, I'm feeling your body in my dreams.
I can't sleep at all, hello, Morning sun.
My love, my crush, wanna tell you my feeling.
Please tell me now
How do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Everytime, everywhere,
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke...
I'm a natural girl, but you're a prince for me
I'm a country girl, but you're a super city boy
Everytime, wondering how I become your girl
Every night, I'm feeling your body in my dreams
I can't sleep at all
Hello morning sun
My love, my crush, wanna tell you my feeling
Please tell me now
How do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Everytime, everywhere,
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke...
Please tell me now
How do you feel me?
Please show me now
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Everytime, everywhere,
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke...
Let's go!
Carbonated Love
[Title: Carbonated Love]
Lost in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I IGNORED Before
You left me WANTING MORE
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon LIGHTS fly by, is it FAKE or REALITY?
Not sure of much but know I'm ready
Soaring these STREETS Make me COMPLETE
Full throttle, COME GIVE ME YOUR ALL
Engine's not
Keeping up With the BEAT of my heart
Just CAN'T Get Enough
REVVING UP, MAKE IT FAST
ONLY US, MAKE IT LAST
TILL THE SUN'S UP
'Nother shot in the dark, TAKE ME AWAY
Fizzing up in my HEART, It's all ok
ACCELERATE ME UNTIL I'M THERE
YOU AND I
Reach the line, MARK The END
But WE'LL
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't CARE if i don't see another day
SHOCKING IN MY HEART
GIVE Me ALL that you Got
Windows down, DON'T HESITATE A MINUTE MORE
TIME IS UP, NOT ENOUGH
FILL IT UP AND DON'T LOOK BACK AGAIN
Carbonated Love
One, two, three, let's go!
It's better on LOVE
[Text: It's better on LOVE]
It's better than I could have dreamed
Look at what we've done, we're too extreme
Pour me your favorite drink, so much until we sink
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues
Race through the night, my guiding light
Sparkling, I'm right here with you
Engine's hot, keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast, only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
Nother' shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up, then look back again
Carbonated love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, the race begins, let's make it new
Let me defy the way, I'm crazy just for you
Nother' shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, rev it up again
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up and begin
Carbonated love
Hoo! Hi RyS! It's IRyS from Hololive English Promise!
Look at who we have here! Aren't they so cute?
かわいいすね、こいつら。
Aren't they cute, these guys.
頑張ってね、一緒に踊っていただいたんで。
They did their best, dancing along with me.
わーい、嬉しい！
Yay, I'm so happy!
And... before we, you know, get into all sorts of things...
First off, please use the hashtag #IRySBDay2026. This way! IRySBDay2026!
こちらのハッシュタグ是非是非ツイートしてくださいね、感想など。
Please tweet using this hashtag with your thoughts and such.
If you have anything you want to talk about this live, please use the hashtag.
See, these guy-Rys will definitely get on their phones later on, too, to tweet with the hashtag.
Have you guys noticed something different?
なんか、アイリスいつもと見た目違うでしょ？
IRyS looks a bit different from usual, right?
どう？
How is it?
Race Queen!
あ、興奮してる。
Ah, they're excited.
They look very excited.
Yeah, oh, they're going mad, yes.
それぐらい素晴らしいでしょ。
It's that wonderful, isn't it?
Finally, the Race Queen outfit is real!
いや、いいね。ありがとうございます。
Yeah, it's good. Thank you very much.
サクラじゃないよ！
They're not shills!
All righty then. First off, though, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods!
Yes, here is the lineup this time!
Yes, we're introducing merch pretty early on this time.
この辺かな？
Around here, maybe?
グッズは今回こちらになります！
Here is the merchandise this time!
Yes, the IRyS Birthday Celebration 2026.
アイリス生誕...えと、誕生日記念2026年。
IRyS Birth... uh, Birthday Celebration 2026.
All right, let me introduce the goods one by one.
First off, there's this one! Hoi!
喜んでるね！
Everyone's so happy!
First up, we have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS!
Illustrations by the beautiful Inonopisu-sensei!
こちらの衣装もピスケ先生なんですよ。
This outfit is also by Pisu-sensei!
This diorama stand features IRyS...
...in her race queen outfit, perfectly capturing
the atmosphere of this 3D live stage! Yes!
みんなも買うよね！
Everyone's buying it, right?
Yes! Hi!
And then the second one is this one!
Yes! The ChibiRyS Tote Bag! It's so cute!
Illustration on the tote bag is by Lien-sensei!
いつもLien先生、ありがとう、
It's always Lien-sensei, thank you,
Thank you so much Lien all the time! So cute!
This tote features mini IRyS in her casual outfit!
Yes, drawn by Lien-sensei, so cute!
Lien先生に描いてもらった、カジュアルアイリス...
Drawn by Lien-sensei, it's casual IRyS...
...ちびになってますの、可愛いトート。
...in chibi form, what a cute tote bag.
ぜひ普段使いしてください。
Please use it for your everyday needs.
お出かけで使ってね！はい！
Use it when you go out! Yes!
Please use it when you go shopping and whatnot!
With this simple design, it's perfect for daily use!
You can pair it with other merch following this...
...so show off your IRyS pride! Yay!
あの、この後に紹介するグッズとも合わせて...
You can use it together with the merch coming up...
...楽しみにしててね！はい！
...so please look forward to it! Yes!
And then the third one is...
...the Race QueenRyS Keychain!
こちらの素晴らしい衣装のキーチェーンです。
It's a keychain of this wonderful outfit.
可愛いやろ？あ、欲しいの？
Isn't it cute? Oh, you want it?
Yeah, I think they want it already!
まだダメ！ここからだよ！
Not yet! It starts from here!
え、注文するよね？
You're going to order it, right?
You guys are going to buy it, right? Yeah!
もう1セットで終わらないよね？
You won't stop at just one set, right?
うん、うん、もう...
Yeah, yeah...
...爆買いしてくれるそうです！はい！
...they say they're going on a shopping spree! Yes!
This is the new plushie featuring my new outfit!
新衣装のアイリスがぬいぐるみのキーホルダーに！
New outfit IRyS has become a plushie keychain!
It's cute on its own, but you can also carry it...
...with its face peeking out from the tote pocket!
ぜひトートバッグの中にバーン！と入れちゃって...
Please pop it right into the tote bag...
...一緒にお出かけしてね！
...and go out together!
And then the last one is the... YabaiRyS Pouch!
Yes! みんなの大好きなヤバイリスだよ！
Yes! It's everyone's favorite YabaiRyS!
何を考えてるんでしょう？
I wonder what she's thinking?
I wonder what she's thinking with that face?
Yes, YabaiRyS is back again!
This face pouch with its high impact design...
...yes, it's high impact!
Can also be attached to the bag handle!
さあ先ほど紹介したトートバッグの...
Now, as for that tote bag I introduced earlier...
...取っ手にバーン！と付けるととっても可愛いよ！
...if you pop it on the handle, it's so cute!
Yes, you can use it with the tote bag...
...and it'll be a perfect set!
Tote, plushie, and pouch as a three-piece set...
...show off your IRyS love around the world! Yes!
This is a pouch, by the way, just clarifying.
これはポーチになってます。Tiny things go in it.
This is a pouch. Tiny things go in it.
Okay, and then here are the full set bonuses!
Yes! The postcard!
Illustration is the same from Pisuke-sensei...
...for the acrylic stand.
ピスケ先生のイラストをポストカードでも！
Pisu-sensei's illustration is also on the postcard!
Limited edition has a handwritten message! Yes!
数量限定版は直筆メッセージ & 箔押し複製サイン...
Limited edition has a handwritten message & signature...
...箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードです！
...duplicate signature postcard!
メッセージは直筆の方です。はい！
The message is the handwritten part. Yes!
So, you guys are buying limited, right? Yeah!
I want you guys to be as hyped as them! Yeah!
Standard version has a foil-stamped autograph...
...and message as well.
通常版も箔押し複製サイン & メッセージ入り...
The standard version also has a signature & message...
...ポストカードです。So you can get both!
...postcard. So you can get both!
限定版も通常版もぜひゲットしてね！ Yeah!
Both limited and standard, please get them! Yeah!
みんな可愛いな。You guys are so cute.
Everyone's so cute. You guys are so cute.
ああ、ああ、they're so cute.
Ah, ah, they're so cute.
Look at how big their heads are.
頭でかいね。
Their heads are huge.
あ、刺される。あ、痛いよ！痛い！痛い！痛いよ！
Ah, I'm getting poked. Ah, it hurts! It hurts!
ああ... もう君たちはしょうがないな。
Ah... you guys are hopeless.
Plenty more announcements coming up! Yeah!
If you can tell, I'm already introducing merch...
...so there's a lot of other things coming up.
この後もね、色んな大きな告知があるんで...
After this too, there are various big announcements...
...ぜひ最後まで見ててくださいね。
...so please watch until the end.
楽しみにしててね。
Please look forward to it.
Big announcements coming, so stay tuned!
じゃあ、続きやるぞ！ Let's go!
Now, let's continue! Let's go!
JANE DOE
[Song: JANE DOE]
まるでこの世界で二人だけみたいだね
As if in this world, only you and I remain
なんて少しだけ夢をみてしまっただけ
Yet in a dream, I allowed myself a moment of longing
つま先に月明かり
Moonlight spills upon the instep
花束の香り
The scent of flowers drifts faintly
指に触れる指
Fingertips lightly touch fingertips
さよなら もう行かなきゃ
Goodbye, it's time for me to go
何もかも忘れて
And forget everything
硝子の上を
Barefoot, step by step,
裸足のまま歩く
on shards of glass
痛むごとに
Each step is excruciating,
血が流れて落ちていく
leaving pools of blood
お願い
Please,
その赤い足跡を辿って
follow these crimson footprints
会いにきて
Come find me
錆びたプールに放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released into a rust-stained swimming pool
靴箱の中隠した林檎
And the apple hidden in the shoe locker
萎びた君の肌に残る傷跡
The scar carved into your withered skin
犬のように泳いだ迷子
A lost child struggling like a drowning dog
どこにいるの
Where are you?
(ここにいるよ)
(I'm right here)
何をしているの
What are you doing?
(ずっと見てるよ)
(I've been watching over you)
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let fallacies overflow this world
側にいてよ
Stay with me,
遊びに行こうよ
let's play once more
どこにいるの
Where in the world are you?
硝子の上を
Barefoot on shards of glass,
裸足のまま歩く
taking step after step
痛むごとに
Each step stings unbearably,
血が流れて落ちていく
leaving pools of blood behind
お願い
Please,
その赤い足跡を辿って
follow these crimson footprints
会いにきて
Come find me
まるでこの世界で
As if in this world,
二人だけみたいだね
only you and I remain
なんて少しだけ
Yet in my dreams,
夢をみてしまっただけ
I indulged in a fleeting moment
Gaze on Me!
[Song: Gaze on Me!]
揺らせ 一秒 駆けたら Summer girls
Shake it! Summer girls, the first second you start galloping
夢への道はストレート
The path to your dream is just straightforward
視線 誰にも 譲れない
This sight, forbidden to anyone
Please, Gaze on Me！
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
Surely, it's the start of a fantastic time
(La la la la la la...)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(... The goal is to be under the spotlight)
(La la la la la la...)
(I'm the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(... Give yours to me)
(Please, Gaze on Me！)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(きっと始まる Fantastic time)
(Surely, it's the start of a fantastic time)
みんな 準備はいいですか？ Burning
Are you ready to burn, everyone?
うなずいて陽炎も Heat up
Agreeing, even heat haze is heating up
どうしよう...
What to do...
どうしよう上昇アガる空気 Let's go!
What should I do? The air is pumping us up! Let's go!
さあ太陽燃えて最高 Mate
Come on, sun, burn bright! You're the best, mate!
負けられない興奮もハートも
I can't lose, not my excitement, not my heart!
駆け引きは No no Gate
No more bargaining! Once the gate...
開いたなら一瞬のドラマ
...opens, it's a momentary drama!
走れ夏の方へ!
Run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒駆けたら Summer girls
Shake it off! If we run for just a second, we'll be Summer girls!
夢への道はストレート
The path to our dreams is a straight line!
視線誰にも譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze!
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely about to stir!
(La la la la la la...)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(My goal is the spotlight!)
(La la la la la la...)
(I'm the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(I want you for myself!)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(きっと沸き立つ Fantastic time)
(A fantastic time is surely about to stir!)
絶対最上掴みたい Feeling
I want to grasp the very best feeling!
全身全霊めぐるから Get hot
It flows through my body and soul, so get hot!
テンション高揚欲しいモノへ
Tensions rise as I head towards my desires,
今 Ride on time
now is the time to ride!
ノって It's show time
Get into it! It's show time!
Peak
迎えるとき遠慮はいらない
There's no need to hesitate when we reach the peak!
せめぎあい Oh oh
Duke it out, oh oh!
Spark
汗とプライドジレた運命
My sweat and pride, and my impatient fate...
連れて夏の方へ!
...take them toward the summer!
挑む世界は魅惑の Sunlight floor
The world I challenge is this captivating sunlight floor!
天井知らずのボルテージ
Our voltage knows no limits!
火照る季節をモノにして
Let's make this scorching season ours!
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい Exciting time
I want to blow your mind with this exciting time!
(La la la la la la...)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(My goal is the spotlight!)
(La la la la la la...)
(I'm the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(I want you for myself!)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(クラリさせたい Exciting time)
(I want to blow your mind with this exciting time!)
関係ないどんな私だって
It doesn't matter who I am,
真夏駆け出せたら Venus
once I dash off into midsummer, I'll be a Venus!
アツくなれば一歩で
One step into the heat,
Change & happy
and I'll change and be happy!
眩しすぎる今日を
I'll take this blindingly bright today,
踊るように手にしよう
and make it mine, as if I'm dancing!
(さぁ Here we go!)
(Now, here we go!)
ビートは止まらない Keep
The beat won't stop! Keep!
Keep
思うままに身を預けて
Entrust yourself to your heart's desires,
灼熱へ Go go
and head into the heat! Go go!
Warp
本能のリズム打ち鳴らして
Beat the rhythm of your instincts,
走れ夏の方へ!
and run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒駆けたら Summer girls
Shake it off! If we run for just a second, we'll be Summer girls!
夢への道はストレート
The path to our dreams is a straight line!
視線誰にも譲れない
I won't let anyone else have your gaze!
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる Fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely about to start!
(La la la la la la...)
(ゴールは Spot light)
(My goal is the spotlight!)
(La la la la la la...)
(I'm the heroine)
(キミを頂戴)
(I want you for myself!)
(Please, Gaze on Me!)
(きっと始まる Fantastic time)
(A fantastic time is surely about to start!)
愛♥スクリーム！
[Song: Ai♥Scream!]
教えて! もっとあなたの事
Tell me! More about you!
(Tell me more, more, more, more)
聞かせて! もっとあなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice!
(Let me hear more, more, more)
こんなドキドキ もう抑え切れない
I can't hold back this excitement anymore!
(All I need you, Oh! All I need you)
友達は卒業 運命の私
Graduating from being friends... Me, your destiny,
見つけて欲しいの
I want you to find me!
(One) 勇気を出して
(One) Gather up some courage!
(Two) 見つめる作戦
(Two) Staring strategy!
(Three) 目と目が合えば
(Three) If our eyes meet,
(Fall) 止められない
(Fall) I won't be able to stop!
Yeah, yeah, yeah
この恋この愛で Melt, melty
With this love, this passion, melt, melty,
溶けちゃうよ ねぇ? ねぇ? ねぇ?
I'm gonna melt away! Hey? Hey? Hey?
気づいて my darling
Notice me, my darling!
届け! 大好き!
Reach me! I love you!
アイ 愛、スクリ~ム scream
I love, scream, scream,
叫びましょ (スクリーム! アイスクリーム!)
let's shout! (Scream! Ice cream!)
Ok! アイ 愛、スクリ~ム! Scream
OK! I love, scream! Scream!
叫びましょ (スクリーム! アイスクリーム!)
let's shout! (Scream! Ice cream!)
フブちゃん! 何が好き?
Fubu-chan! What do you like?
フブちゃん！
Fubu-chan!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミント よりも あ・な・た
More than chocolate mint, I like you.
アイリスちゃん！
IRyS-chan!
はーい！
Hi!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレイバー よりも あ・な・た
More than strawberry flavor, I like you.
ミオちゃん！
Mio-chan!
はーい！
Hi!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー＆クリーム よりも あ・な・た
More than cookies and cream, I like you.
みんなー！
Everyone!
はーい！
Hi!
何が好き？
What do you like?
モチロン大好き AiScReam
Of course we love AiScReam
止められない YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
Unstoppable, YEAH YEAH YEAH, with this love, with this affection
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよねぇ？
Melt melty, I'm melting, right?
ねぇ？ねぇ？
Right? Right?
気づいて “my darling”
Notice me, “my darling”
届け！ 大好き！
Reach out! I love you!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
I, Ai, Scream, SCREAM, let's shout it out
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK！
OK!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
I, Ai, Scream, SCREAM, let's shout it out
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
おねがい見つけて “my darling”
Please find me, “my darling”
おねがい気づいて “my darling”
Please notice me, “my darling”
One
勇気を出して
Muster your courage
Two
近づく作戦
The approach strategy
Three
手と手が触れて
Our hands touch
Fall 止められない
Fall, it's unstoppable
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
YEAH YEAH YEAH, with this love, with this affection
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよねぇ？
Melt melty, I'm melting, right?
ねぇ？ねぇ？
Right? Right?
気づいて “my darling”
Notice me, “my darling”
それは！ アナタ！
That's! You!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
I, Ai, Scream, SCREAM, let's shout it out
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK！
OK!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
I, Ai, Scream, SCREAM, let's shout it out
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
I, Ai, Scream, SCREAM, let's shout it out
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
OK！
OK!
アイ 愛、スクリ～ム SCREAM 叫びましょ
I, Ai, Scream, SCREAM, let's shout it out
スクリーム！ アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
La la la la la love love...
モニタリング (Best Friend Remix)
[Title: Monitoring (Best Friend Remix)]
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
知ってるよ ピクンピクン震えてさ 声もだだ漏れなんだわ
I know. You're shaking and trembling, and your voice is leaking out.
正直に言っちゃえば バレてるんだし言っちゃえば
To be honest, it's already obvious, so just say it.
聞いてんの？ 普通普通 平気だよ みんなわかってないだけ
Are you listening? It's okay, it's normal. Everyone else just doesn't get it.
うつ
Depression.
もしもし。 ねえ、大丈夫？
Hello? Hey, are you okay?
んー、心配だから今からそっち行くね
Hmm, I'm worried, so I'm coming over now.
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの
Hey, I know. I know you're crying all alone.
知ってるよ クスンクスン凹んでさ 弱音ヒトからいんじゃない？
I know. You're sobbing and feeling down, isn't it okay to show some weakness?
朝が来るまで一緒トーク もっと泣いたって
We'll talk together until morning. Even if you cry more,
何度だって受け止めてあげる もう我慢しないでいっぱい吐いてね
I'll catch you every time. Don't hold back anymore, let it all out.
うわ！
Whoa!
お願いきみが欲しいの 慰めさせてベストフレンド 愛の才能で
Please, I want you. Let me comfort you, best friend, with the talent of love.
泣いてくれるかい きみのつらい 抱きしめたい ねぇいいでしょ？
Will you cry for me? Your pain, I want to embrace it, is that okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいんだ 暖かくなれば
I want to share it and overcome it together. If it gets warmer...
うわ！
Whoa!
お願いきみが欲しいの 笑い飛ばしてホップステップジャンプ最高ぜ
Please, I want you. Let's laugh it off, hop-step-jump, it's the best!
分けてくれるかい きみに重い 暗い思い ねぇいいでしょ？
Will you share it with me? Your heavy, dark thoughts, is that okay?
寄り添って 救いたいんだ 暖かくなれば
I want to be close and save you. If it gets warmer...
見たい見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see...
見たいのきみの中
I want to see inside of you
見たい見たい見たい見たい...
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see...
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり悔しがってるの
Hey, I know. I know you're feeling frustrated all alone.
知ってるよ グスングスン終わるまで きみを決して諦めない
I know. Until the sobbing ends, I will never give up on you.
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみはできる子知ってるよ
Hey, I know. I know you're a capable person.
つらい時は 弱いくらいでちょうどいい あたしきみの味方だよ
When it's tough, being a bit weak is just right. I'm on your side.
うわ！
Whoa!
お願いきみが欲しいの 名前を呼んでよ いつだって会いに参上
Please, I want you. Call my name, I'll come to see you anytime.
きみはひとりかい？ それは違う ひとりじゃない もういいでしょ？
Are you alone? That's not right. You're not alone, is that enough?
ソロプレイはおしまいなんだ 暖かくなれば
Solo play is over now. If it gets warmer...
きみがどんなときも あたし側にいるわ
No matter when, I'll be by your side.
いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
I'm always watching over you. That's right, there's nothing to be afraid of.
Mwah! お願い
Mwah! Please
お願い きみが欲しいの
I beg of you, I want you
慰めさせて ベストフレンド
Let me comfort you, best friend
愛の才能で
With the talent of love
泣いてくれるかい きみのツライ
Will you cry for me? Your pain...
抱きしめたい ねえいいでしょう？
...I want to embrace it, hey is that okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいんだ
I want us to share it and overcome it together
だっだってば
I'm telling you!
お願い きみが欲しいの
I beg of you, I want you
笑い飛ばして ホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ
Laugh it off, hop step jump
最高さ
It's the best!
分けてくれるかい きみの重い
Will you share with me? Your heavy...
暗い思い 取り除きたい
...dark thoughts, I want to take them away
吸い取って 救いたいんだ
I want to absorb them and save you
だっだってば
I'm telling you!
ねぇ私知ってるよ
Hey, I know...
君が独りきりで泣いてるの
...that you're crying all by yourself
グスングスン凹んでさ
Sniffling and feeling down
弱音ヒトカラいいんじゃない？
Isn't it okay to vent your weaknesses at solo karaoke?
ずっと一緒もっと泣いたって
We're always together, so even if you cry more
何度だって受け止めてあげる
I'll accept you no matter how many times it takes
もう立ち直り手出して
Now, reach out your hand to recover
だっだってば
I'm telling you!
Promise 02-29 / 03-07 / 03-14
[On-screen Text: Promise 02-29 / 03-07 / 03-14]
Go Beat Crazy!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go!
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go!
Go Beat Crazy!
Beat, beat, baby
Music gets you crazy
Shock me tonight
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Fun, fun, baby
Dancing feeling hazy
Shake out of sight
(Go Beat Crazy!)
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad!
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go! Go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go! Go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Boom, boom, baby
Come and shake your booty
Dig it tonight
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Go, go, baby
Show me that you're ready
Get satisfied
(Go Beat Crazy!)
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad!
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go! Go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go! Go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go!
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go!
Go Beat Crazy!
Everybody dance!
Everybody groove!
Everybody go! Go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go!
(Go Beat Crazy!)
GO BEAT CRAZY
[Song: GO BEAT CRAZY]
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go, go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Are you ready?
カリスマックス
[Song: Charismax]
Everybody make some noise
誰も真似できやしないな
Nobody can copy the formula
StarのGuidance CHARISMA
Star-led Guidance CHARISMA
バズりまくり
Trending, we're makin' it
常にTacticalに CHARISMA
Always we're tactical, CHARISMA
Haterたちにご提案
Haters, I gotta tell ya
ディスるより Do what you love CHARISMA
Don't give a damn, do what you love CHARISMA
朝から晩までRing a Ring a ling
All day long, let it Ring a Ring a ling
勝ちや負け 気にするの論外
Win? Lose? That's not the “Problem”
「ミスるの問題」
“A minor mistake”
とか言ってんのが大問題
The mindset, that's the “Problem”
Alright 自分が正解
Alright, I'm gonna define
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone push ahead with strong heart
We are！ We are！ No.1 CHARISMAX
We are! We are! No.1 CHARISMAX
最強のマインド CHARISMAX
The one and only mind CHARISMAX
時代塗り替える CHARISMAX
Now rewrite the age CHARISMAX
世界が驚く
We gon gasp the world
どいつもこいつも Crazy Crazy man
Better watch us, everyone is Crazy crazy man
常識壊してゆく CHARISMAX
Much beyond the common sense, we are CHARISMAX
まるで人生はStageみたいだ
Don't you see life's like a stage we stand on
皆が役者 CHARISMA
Doing a role-play CHARISMA
何でもできる そう君は何でもできる CHARISMA
You can do anything, right, I know that you can be anything CHARISMA
Wannabeたちにご提案
Wannabes, I gotta tell ya
今すぐに Do what you want CHARISMA
Don't give a damn, do what you want CHARISMA
世界に響かすDing a Ding a ling
Sing along, let's get it, Ding a ding a ling
空気は読むより変えてくStyle
Let me change it all, it's my style
はみ出す天才
Sticking out genius
てか愛想笑いなんてしない
No fake smiles, make it right
Alright 答えは明快
Alright, answer's generous
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone push ahead with strong heart
We are！ We are！ No.1 CHARISMAX
We are! We are! No.1 CHARISMAX
才能解き放つ CHARISMAX
The talent's not an imitation CHARISMAX
進化をし続ける CHARISMAX
Unstoppable evolution CHARISMAX
限界超えてゆく
Go beyond the limitation
どいつもこいつも Crazy Crazy woman
Better watch us, everyone is Crazy crazy woman
Everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone push ahead with strong heart
We are！ We are！...
We are! We are!...
No.1
最強のマインド CHARISMAX
The one and only mind CHARISMAX
時代塗り替える CHARISMAX
Now rewrite the age CHARISMAX
世界が驚く
We gon gasp the world
どいつもこいつも Crazy Crazy man
Better watch us, everyone is Crazy crazy man
才能解き放つ CHARISMAX
The talent's not an imitation CHARISMAX
進化をし続ける CHARISMAX
Unstoppable evolution CHARISMAX
限界超えてゆく
Go beyond the limitation
どいつもこいつも Crazy Crazy woman
Better watch us, everyone is Crazy crazy woman
常識壊してゆく CHARISMAX
Much beyond the common sense, we are CHARISMAX
Please wait...
FOCUS
[Song: FOCUS]
Can I get it, get it, get all your attention?
I bet you don’t know me yet
君の奥底まで 穿つ目線で
A gaze that sees through the depths of you
溢れる様 IQ ammo
It's like it keeps flowing, my IQ ammo
獲る天下
Easily the best in the world
A catalyst, I know. When I say go, put your hands up!
混沌の最中に
All within the chaos
降臨した女神
A goddess befalls from above
I freeze it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know but you don’t
震撼させる 異脳
My out of this world wisdom that shakes this world
I'mma go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine
Can't stop きらめく my fantasy
Can't stop my fantasy that twinkles
Now you see
星空を 丸ごと
I engulf the starlit sky whole
染めるんだ 私色に
And dye it into my hue
Hidden deep within my universe
Come find me now
Hear the voice that’s calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を
I'll show you the truth of this world
見せてあげるから
That's never been seen before, so
Baby, for now
Calm down, lemme focus
Under my spell like hypnosis
So don’t get too close when I’m
(Come-a, come-a, comin' through)
You wanna roll with me?
We take 'em down
Yes, I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do
脳髄まで bulletproof
Down to my spinal fluid, I'm bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do, when I focus
On me, back at my best, I finesse
私の脳裏に 潜む怪物
The monster that is my intelligence
No secret
冷静に cool... my attitude
Keepin' it cool, my attitude
Uh-uh, target in my sight
Locked in, ready to shoot, like
Mayday, this is an emergency
Working under pressure
Baby, I can do this in my sleep
世のことわりだって 書き換えてしまうような頭脳
The brains that can even rewrite all reasons in the universe
When I go, when I go, Imma shine, shine, shine, shine
Won't stop きらめく my fantasy
Won't stop my fantasy that twinkles
Now you see
銀河を ネイロで外側 震わすように
I'll make this sound echo through the universe
Hidden deep within my universe
Come find me now
Clear my mind of all these doubts
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄 この目で見たいから
I wanna see the truths of this world
Baby, for now
Calm down, lemme focus
Under my spell like hypnosis
So don’t get too close when I’m
(Come-a, come-a, comin' through)
You wanna roll with me?
We take 'em down
Yes, I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do
脳髄まで bulletproof
Down to my spinal fluid, I'm bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do, when I focus
垂れろ頭
Bow your heads
Don't break my focus
Wanna try and play catch up?
Follow my mind
I'mma get you talkin' 'bout it loud
Can't get rid of me now
逐一 so I’m crowned
One by one, so I'm crowned
Put my feet on the ground
真っ逆さま 飛べ
Fly headfirst
Piece of cake, it's no stress
銀河中を魅了して
Fascinating the whole galaxy
What's next? Take a guess, yes
I tell you what to do
I got nothing to prove
Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do
脳髄まで bulletproof
Down to my spinal fluid, I'm bulletproof
Cold when I do what I do, when I focus
垂れろ頭
Bow your heads
Don't break my focus
Wanna try and play catch up?
Follow my mind
Focus.
DARK ARIA
[Song: DARK ARIA ]
The time has come
to pack away all the joys
You don't wanna hear my apology
Get it off my chest
I would do my best
I know what you fear
Similarities
we possess
Never will I pass the test
The scene is fading
Can my soul be put to rest?
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairytales?
Far from this tragedy
Sad you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels wings
lifting and setting me free
Death is gonna come for me
Be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairytales?
Far from this tragedy
Sad you had to wait for me
Feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins
Angels wings
lifting and setting me free
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
Woo! Oh, we're getting towards the end of the live.
There were so many beautiful songs...
...and so many beautiful guests!
I love the glasses, the Karisuma X Daisuke glasses. Good stuff!
And we're getting to the end, which means announcements! Yay!
Oh, but first off, before this live—I mean, after this live...
...there will be a members-only part as well, so join the Nefamily today!
えっと、この後もね、あのメン限パートもあるので...
And after this, there will also be a members-only part...
...ぜひメンバーに、メンバーシップに入ってこーい！イエーイ！
...so please join the membership! Yay!
歌うんでね。Yes! Ah, okay then.
I'll be singing there. Yes! Ah, okay then.
Are you guys ready for the announcement?
すごく、すごく嬉しい告知があります！
I have a very, very happy announcement to make!
It's a big, big announcement, I'm really, really happy about it.
I can't wait! I'm super happy I get to share it with you guys.
はい、嬉しい告知、行きます！
Alright, here comes the happy announcement!
まずは、こちらをご覧ください！ Please watch this short video.
First, please take a look at this! Please watch this short video.
願いを叶える魔法があるとするなら
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes
それは、あなた。
It would be you
2026 Oct 6th
JAPAN TOKYO
IRyS 1st Concert
VENUE: SGC HALL ARIAKE
そしてわたしは、あなたに贈る
I will gift you with
奇跡で出来た、この希望を。
Hope made of miracles
ということで！ Yes!
And so! Yes!
IRyS, I will be having my very first solo live! Yay!
In Tokyo, Japan! アイリスなんと...
In Tokyo, Japan! IRyS will actually...
初めてのソロライブ、日本で開催されることが決定しました！ウッフー！
...have her first solo live, and it's decided it'll be held in Japan! Woo-hoo!
Yes! It will be in Tokyo at the SGC Hall Ariake.
えっと、場所は東京のSGCホール有明でございます！
The venue is SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo!
日程は10月6日。It's gonna be on a Tuesday.
The date is October 6th. It's gonna be on a Tuesday.
はい、火曜日でございますね。It'll be happening on...
Yes, it's a Tuesday. It'll be happening on...
...October 6th, Tuesday! Yeah! Mark your calendars!
カレンダーに書いといてや！ずっとね...
Write it on your calendars! For a long time...
本当に夢に見ていたステージに立てること、すごく嬉しく思いますし...
...I've dreamed of standing on this stage, and I'm so happy...
...本当にみんなの応援のおかげです。ありがとうございます！
...it's all thanks to everyone's support. Thank you so much!
It's all thanks to you guys' support that I get to have this opportunity.
So thank you so much for all your support until now! 頑張るぞー！
So thank you so much for all your support until now! I'll do my best!
えっとね、I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one...
You know, I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one...
...for you guys, a very magical one! So please look forward to it.
Make sure you definitely come! If you don't come, I'll be sad.
If you don't come, you'll also regret it! Yes!
あのライブに向けて、準備めちゃくちゃ頑張ってるんで！
I'm working super hard on the preparations for the live!
素晴らしいライブになるように頑張ってるんで、ぜひ会場へ見に来てください！
I'm doing my best to make it a wonderful live, so please come to the venue!
見に行かないとアイリス悲しいし、みんなも後悔するぞ！はい！
If you don't go, IRyS will be sad, and you'll regret it too! Yes!
そして！ And, along with it! Yes!
And! And, along with it! Yes!
I will also be releasing my very first full album! Woo-hoo!
なんとアイリス、初のフルアルバム、出ます！
Actually, IRyS's first full album is coming out!
なんだかんだ言ってね、今までEPだったんですけど、フルアルバムは初めてです！
Believe it or not, I've only released EPs until now, so this is my first full album!
Yeah, I've released EPs in the past, but this is the very first full album.
So look forward to it, there's a lot of songs! The album jacket...
じゃじゃーん！ Yeah, album jacket is by Kito Koruta-sensei!
Ta-da! Yeah, the album jacket is by Kito Koruta-sensei!
It's very cute! The album title is called 'DANGEROUS'. Yes!
何でも'RIS'を付ければいいってもんじゃないかもしれないけど...
It might not be as simple as just putting 'RIS' at the end of everything...
...ちょうどはまったんでね、'DANGEROUS'な、とっても危険的でホットなアルバムになってます！
...but it fit perfectly, so 'DANGEROUS'—it's a very risky and hot album!
Yes! It is written by—I mean, there are many songs written by all sorts of songwriters...
And there's gonna be a lot of Eurobeat songs but also songs that are not Eurobeat as well, new genres as well. So, I hope you guys look forward to that.
ね、あの国内外の様々なクリエイターにユーロビート以外の楽曲も多数作ってもらってます。
Domestic and overseas creators have made many non-Eurobeat tracks as well.
A lot of new songs.
And I will be performing of course, performing one of the songs for you today.
今日もね、あの1曲披露しようかなと思ってます。
I'm planning to perform one song today too.
Showcase yay!
The song I'll be showcasing for you today was written and arranged by the Eurobeat circle SOUND HOLIC-san! Woohoo!
Yes, they're very famous for Eurobeat so I'm really glad, I'm really happy to be able to work with them. Thank you so much.
えっとね、今回披露する楽曲は、作曲、編曲、国内のユーロビートを得意とするクリエイターさん、SOUND HOLICさんでございます。ありがとうございます。
The song I'll be performing today is composed and arranged by the domestic Eurobeat expert creators, SOUND HOLIC. Thank you very much.
新たなユーロビートの見せ方になると思うんで楽しみに指定て。
I think it'll show a new side of Eurobeat, so please look forward to it.
It's Eurobeat but there's something about it that's also not very Eurobeat, so I hope you guys know what I mean when I sing it.
Yes, um, the digital release will be happening on 12 AM JST, the upcoming 12 AM JST after this. So make sure you stream it on Spotify and other streaming services. Yeah!
この後ね、えっとデジタルリリースも各配信サイトで行われます。えっと、0時に配信されます。
After this, the digital release will also be on various streaming sites. It'll be released at midnight.
楽しみにしててね。
Please look forward to it.
すごいド派手な曲です。楽しみだ。
It's a very flashy song. I'm excited.
Um, and as for the details of the album, I will be um talking about that at the very end of this live, so be sure to stick till the end.
アルバムの詳細は、この後最後のほうでね、えっといろいろ説明しちゃうんで、最後まで見てね。
I'll be explaining the album details later near the end, so watch until then.
All right then.
Please listen to my new song, BE MY FLAME.
新しい曲聞いてください、BE MY FLAME.
Please listen to the new song, BE MY FLAME.
BE MY FLAME
Lyrics: Stephanie Snyder Music: Nana Takahashi
Arrangement: MasKaleido, SOUND HOLIC
[Title: BE MY FLAME]
Lyrics: Stephanie Snyder Music: Nana Takahashi
Arrangement: MasKaleido, SOUND HOLIC
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
(Tension rising to the top,
Won't look back, I'll never stop,
Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot
It's your fault, baby)
Fever burning up inside, it can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
(Come on and come on I wanna confess,
baby oh baby I'm gettin' obsessed)
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
(Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter,
gonna be wanna be ready for more)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
(And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, it's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul,
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play; A dangerous game,
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
(Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash,
breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash)
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
(Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy,
tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love
(And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm only getting started...
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream,
Wild desire fueling my delusion,
I want you burning for me!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
RACING TOWARDS HOPE - BIG ANNOUNCEMENTS!
[Title: RACING TOWARDS HOPE - BIG ANNOUNCEMENTS!]
So, how did you guys like my birthday 3D Live?
We had so much going on from the
new 3D outfit debut, new merch...
...to my first album announcement,
solo live announcement, and new song performances!
I think it was packed with so much, so,
I'd like to give you guys a recap and share the details.
ライブ本編どうでしたか？
How did you like the main live performance?
色々とね、告知盛りだくさんだったと思うので、
There were a lot of announcements, so...
改めておさらいと詳細をお伝えします。
I'll go over the recap and details once more.
まずはグッズから！
First up, the merch!
We have the acrylic diorama StandRyS
illustrated by Inunopisuke-sensei,
the ChibiRyS tote bag illustrated by Leen-sensei,
the Race QueenRyS keychain, which is a
really cute race queen plushie keychain,
and the YabaiRyS pouch.
For full set bonuses, the limited edition includes
a postcard with a handwritten message and autograph.
The standard version includes a postcard with
both a foil-stamped message and autograph.
The sales will start at 1:15 PM, which is like
real soon if not maybe even now.
フルセットを買っていただいた方には、数量限定版は
For those who buy the full set, the limited edition
直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
comes with a handwritten message and replica signature.
通常バージョンは、箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りポストカードになります。
The standard version includes a foil-stamped replica signature and message.
この後1時15分にカートオープンするよ！
The cart opens at 1:15 after this!
もうすぐだよ！
It's coming up soon!
続いてアルバムです。
Next up, the album.
This time, it's being released in two formats,
the CD and vinyl! Woohoo!
Pre-orders will begin also at 1:15 PM JST at the
hololive production official shop, like real soon.
As for digital releases, that will happen on July 12th.
今回はCDとレコードの
This time, it will be released
2種類のリリースとなっておりまして、
in two types: CD and record,
この後1時15分よりホロライブオフィシャルショップにて
and pre-orders will start at 1:15
予約が開始されます。
at the Hololive Official Shop.
デジタルリリースは7月12日です。
The digital release is on July 12th.
CDにはここでしか聴けない、
The CD includes a rearranged version of Gravity
Gravityのリアレンジバージョンとステッカー2種類。
and two types of stickers that can only be heard here.
レコードにはジャケットとアナザージャケットが印刷された
The record comes with an LP-sized double-sided
LPサイズ両面ポスターカードがついてきます。
poster card with both jacket illustrations.
ポストカードじゃないよ、ポスターカード。もっとデカいです。
It's not a postcard, it's a poster card. Much bigger.
さらにこちらのポスターカードには
Furthermore, this poster card will
両面のどちらかに必ず直筆サインが入ります！
definitely have a handwritten signature on one side!
サインされる面はランダムでございます。
The side that is signed is random.
裏面かもしれないし、表面かもしれません。
It could be the back or the front.
The CD will include an exclusive rearranged
version of Gravity and two types of stickers,
while the vinyl comes with a
double-sided LP-sized poster card,
yes a pretty darn big poster card, featuring
both the main and alternate album covers.
Plus, yes a big plus, one side of this poster card
will definitely feature a handwritten autograph.
The signed side will be random, so it could be on
either the alternate jacket side or the main album cover.
And BE MY FLAME, which was performed in today's
3D Live, will also be digitally released at midnight today!
So don't forget to check it out!
そしてライブでお披露目したBE MY FLAMEは
And 'BE MY FLAME' which premiered at the live
24時にデジタルリリースもあるので、忘れずにチェックしてね！
will release at 24:00, so don't forget to check it out!
And there's more!
That's right!
My first solo live concert! Woohoo!
Tokyo at SGC Hall Ariake! Woo!
And it will be held on a Tuesday, on October 6th!
I'm super, super, duper excited for this, and I'm so glad I've got to finally announce it.
So I hope you guys will be really excited for it as well! Yay!
あとね、えっとソロライブも決まりました！
Also, my solo live concert has been confirmed!
場所は東京SGCホール有明でございます。
The venue will be SGC Hall Ariake in Tokyo.
えーと、開催される日程は10月6日火曜日です。
And the date it'll be held is Tuesday, October 6th.
すごく楽しみにしてるし、もうとにかく、もうこんなライブがやれる機会自体がもう本当に、まさかできると思ってなくて...
I'm really looking forward to it, and I honestly never thought I'd have the chance to do a concert like this...
とってもワクワクしてますし、これからも準備頑張ります！
I'm so excited, and I'll do my best with the preparations from here on!
Please look forward to further details and information in the future!
Last but not least, there will be a members only part starting at 1:30 PM...
Pretty soon, so please come check it out if you can and join the IRyS family!
最後に、メンバー限定パートが1時半から始まるので...
Lastly, the members-only encore part starts at 1:30 PM...
よかったらメンバーに入って見に来てね！
So if you'd like, please join the membership and come watch!
では、ありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Bye for now, until the members part!